# Code by Andrew Brodsky | 107217786 | Assignment 0 | Prof: Maciej Zagrodzki 

# Bot will always be on one of three orientations: walls on 2 sides, 3 sides, or no walls on any side

# The Strat (TM): Fill in a wave going from left to right. Move North or South until hitting a corner, then move around the corner and paint in the opposite direction. Once in the far right corner, go all the way west and repeat.

# States: 0 is heading north, 1 is heading south, 2 is heading west, 3 is DRS shotgun, 4 is URS shotgun, 5 is DRN shotgun, 6 is URN shotgun, 7 is mop-up north, 8 is mop-up south

#---------------------------

# going north:
0 x*** -> N 0 # go north first until hitting a north edge
0 NxWS -> E 7 # if started in left corner, start mop-up right away 
0 NExS -> W 2 # if started in right corner, start heading west 

0 NExx -> S 3 # if in upper right nook, reverse direction and trigger DRS shotgun
3 **** -> E 1 # DR shotgun, then go south

0 NxWx -> E 4 # if in upper left nook, move right and URS
4 **** -> N 1 # UR shotgun, then go south

0 NEWx -> S 1 # if in top corner, go south without shotgunning

# going south:

1 N**x -> S 1 # go south away from the wall unless you're in the far right corner
1 xxxx -> S 1 # go south in free space

1 xExS -> N 6 # if in lower right nook, reverse direction and trigger URN shotgun
6 **** -> E 0 # URN shotgun, then go north

1 xxWS -> E 5 # if in lower left nook, go right and trigger DRN shotgun
5 **** -> S 0 # DRN shotgun, then go north

1 xEWS -> N 6 # if in bottom corner, go north, URN shotgun, and continue north

# how to head west:
1 NExS -> W 2 # if in corner, go west
2 **x* -> W 2 # just keep going west until the following line is satisfied
2 NxWS -> E 7 # if in opposite corner, begin the mop-up

# mopping up:
7 **** -> N 8 # start with north mop, then move to south
8 ***x -> S 8 # mop south as long as there's nothing to the south
8 ***S -> E 5 # once all the way south, DRN shotgun and continue

